respawn.com 2019-02-27

# Privacy Policy - Respawn Entertainment

##### PRIVACY POLICY

Respawn Entertainment, LLC, a California Limited Liability Company (“Respawn,” “we,” “us,” “our”) respects your privacy rights, and the protection of those rights is important to us. To explain how we collect, store and use personal information collected or received through our Website, we have adopted this Privacy Policy. Personal information is information about you that can be used to identify you as an individual, such as your name, address, e-mail address or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

This Privacy Policy applies only to personal information collected or received through our Website. It does not apply to other information that you submit to us or to any information that we receive in other ways. This Privacy Policy only applies only to Respawn. It does not apply to the practices of companies that Respawn does not own or control, or to people that Respawn does not employ or manage.

Be sure to return to this page periodically to ensure familiarity with the most current version of this Agreement. We reserve the right at any time, with or without cause, to change the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. Any changes we make will be effective immediately upon our making such changes available on the Website or otherwise providing notice thereof. You agree that your continued use of the Website, Proprietary Information, Services, or Games after such changes constitutes your acceptance of such changes.

##### Information Collection and Use

Respawn collects personal information when you register on the Website, when you visit Website pages, and when you enter certain promotions. You are not required to submit any personal information to Respawn, and you can use many areas of our Website without submitting any personal information to us. Some areas of our Website are only accessible if you decide to give us some personal information. For example, only registered users can make full use of our forums, and to register you must submit your full name, email address, and birthdate. You may also submit additional information that may enhance your experience, including your Steam ID, Playstation Network ID, Xbox LIVE Gamertag, website URL, location, and/or a short bio. You may also choose to sign up for an email newsletter or other online services we may offer, which we may use to send you updates and other information about Respawn and our Website, Services, and Games.

The Website also automatically receives and records certain information provided by your computer and browser when you use the Website, including your IP address, Respawn ‘cookie’ information, hardware and software attributes, the Website pages requested, and data contained in page requests from referring web pages. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Respawn uses cookies to provide customized content, keep track of your preferences, deliver advertising relevant to your interests and other purposes related to operating and protecting the Website. You can configure your browser to reject cookies, but you will not be able to use any Services or Games that require you to “sign in,” and you may not be able to take full advantage of all Website offerings. The personal information we collect is used to control access to and facilitate the operation of our Website, Services and Games, as well as for communication, research and marketing, as well as for any additional purposes identified in connection with the collection of such information. Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, we may use your personal information to provide customer support; to service our Games’ warranties; to host special events, contests, and other Services; to enforce our Terms of Service; to resolve disputes and troubleshoot problems; and to improve, market or prepare to market our Services and Games or any upgrades or enhancements thereof.

In addition to the personal information we may collect, you may submit additional information by email to us. You should be aware that what we do with such information is expressly addressed and governed by our Terms of Service. We may use such information to respond to your email or for any other purpose permitted by the Terms of Service.

##### Information Sharing and Disclosure

Respawn does not rent, sell or share personal information about you with other people or non- affiliated companies except to control access to and facilitate the operation of our Website, to provide Services and Games you have requested, when we have received your permission, or in the limited circumstances described below:

  * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Respawn under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Respawn operate our Website, Services or Games, and/or help Respawn communicate with you about offers from Respawn and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * We may use or transfer information about you if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.
  * We transfer information about you if Respawn is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Respawn will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

##### Protection Of Information Collected

We maintain safeguards for the purpose of ensuring the confidentiality and security of the personally identifiable information you submit to us. While we believe that these safeguards are adequate and appropriate to protect your confidential information, you should be aware that there is always a possibility of intrusion into secured computer systems, and you should take that into account in deciding whether to submit any personal information to us.

##### Public Information

You may choose to disclose personal or other information about yourself by submitting information to be displayed as part of your public profile, by posting information to our public forums, or in the course of any public method of communication permitted by our Website, Services, or Games. Information that you disclose in any of these manners is public information, and there is no expectation of privacy or confidentiality in such information. Such information can be read, collected, or used by other users of our Website, Services, and Games, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages (and, although such messages may violate our Terms of Service, we are not liable to you as a result of them). We are not responsible for any personal information (or any images, videos, or other media) you choose to submit in these manners. Additionally, any information you submit in these manners is subject to our Terms of Service.

##### Updating Your Personal Information

If you wish to update or cancel your registration, or if you wish to opt out of receiving our newsletter, you may contact us at any time by emailing us at info@respawn.com. After we process your request, we will disable your account or cease contact with you for marketing purposes, as applicable, but we may still retain your information in our files to resolve disputes, to enforce our Terms of Service, and due to technical or legal requirements or constraints.

##### Questions and Comments

If you have any questions, complaints, or comments regarding our Privacy Policy, you may contact us at any time by emailing us at info@respawn.com.

Effective June 28th, 2011
